<?xml:stylesheet href="sample.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<sample>
<title>XMLTree</title>
<author>Oh, Soo-Young.</author>
<dependencies>
<dep>Microsoft Foundation Class Library</dep>
<dep>Microsoft XML Version 2.0 for IE5</dep>
</dependencies>
<description>
This XMLTree application was created using the MFC AppWizard.  This application
uses the IE5 XML Document Object Model to parse and display XML documents 
in a tree-style view.
</description>
<mainlist>
<file>
  <name>XMLTree.dsp</name>
  <contains>
    VC6 project file which contains information used to build a single project or subproject. 
    Other users can share the project (.dsp) file, but they should export the makefiles locally.
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>XMLTree.h</name>
  <contains>
    Main project specific includes (including Resource.h) and declaration of the
    CXMLTreeApp application class.
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>XMLTree.cpp</name>
  <contains>
    The source for the main application class CXMLTreeApp.
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>XMLTree.rc</name>
  <contains>
    All of the Microsoft Windows resources that the program uses.  
    It includes the icons, bitmaps, and cursors that are stored
    in the RES subdirectory.  
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>XMLTree.clw</name>
  <contains>
    Information used by ClassWizard to edit existing
    classes or add new classes.  ClassWizard also uses this file to store
    information needed to create and edit message maps and dialog data
    maps and to create prototype member functions.
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>res\XMLTree.ico</name>
  <contains>
    The application's icon.  This icon is included by the main resource file XMLTree.rc.
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>res\XMLTree.rc2</name>
  <contains>
    Resources that are not edited by Microsoft Visual C++.  
  </contains>
</file>
</mainlist>
<wizlist>
  <description>The following files were generated by the Visual Studio AppWizard</description>
<file>
  <name>XMLTreeDlg.h, XMLTreeDlg.cpp - the dialog</name>
  <contains>
    The source for the CXMLTreeDlg class which is the application's main dialog.
    The dialog's template is in XMLTree.rc, which can be edited in Microsoft Visual C++.
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>StdAfx.h, StdAfx.cpp</name>
  <contains>
    These files are used to build a precompiled header (PCH) file
    named XMLTree.pch and a precompiled types file named StdAfx.obj.
  </contains>
</file>
<file>
  <name>Resource.h</name>
  <contains>
    This is the standard header file, which defines new resource IDs.
    Microsoft Visual C++ reads and updates this file.
  </contains>
</file>
</wizlist>
</sample>